

070-8970-7874 sander.alexia@gmail.com Tokyo-to, Fuchu-shi, Koremasa 5-3-4, Center Village room 305 183-0014 Japan

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With over 5 years of experience in IT Infrastructure focused on digital transformation and user empowerment, I am eager to challenge myself in new areas. Creative and detail-oriented, I am at ease working in a team as well as individually.

EXPERIENCE

Feb. 2017 - current

Digital workplace specialist, IT Infrastructure, Mitsubishi Fuso Truck & Bus Corporation – Kawasaki, Japan

- Responsible for the user helpdesk chatbot/site design and management
- Creation and execution of user oriented IT trainings
- Enhancement of the local IT devices and services ordering platform
- Coordination with other international locations for smooth software and patches distribution via SCCM

Nov. 2016 - Feb. 2017

Japanese to French Translator, Primots SARL - Tokyo, Japan (remote)

 Translation of various types of documents from a travel smartphone application to medication leaflets

Feb. - Aug. 2016

IT Process Design Team Intern, Mitsubishi Fuso Truck & Bus Corporation - Kawasaki, Japan

- IT department events, marketing and communication
- Smartphone application mock-ups design
- Business process mapping

EDUCATION

2011 - 2016

Master's degree in English, Japanese and business studies, Jean Moulin Lyon III University, Lyon, France

- 1 year exchange program at Keio University (Tokyo, Japan)
- Internship dissertation "Culture in international mergers and acquisitions" nominated at the 4th position for the "Grand Prix CCEF Rhône-Alpes" contest

2010-2011

1 year exchange in Otsuma Ranzan high school – Saitama, Japan

Intercultural experience in a Japanese school and Japanese host family

SKILLS

Languages: French – Native level

English - TOEIC: 835/990 - 2012

Japanese - Japanese Language Proficiency Test: N2 (175/180) - 2014

Computer: Microsoft Office Suite, Clip Studio Paint, Visual Studio Code 2

HOBBIES

Creative activities: writing novels, digital drawing

Foreign culture and languages: particular interest in Japan

Programming: learning how to code with HTML, CSS, Ruby on Rails